♪♪
Thank you for watching.
[Phone rings]
One more.
Yes! Good evening!
I've been a recluse my whole life!
I can't fly! No, I can't fly!
I'm Honey, your shut-in idol!
Patapatancho!
Did you eat ice cream?
No, I didn't!
What?
No, I didn't eat.
What are you doing about food?
I haven't breathed fresh air for 5 years, thanks to those expensive lunches.
I want to see your sleeping face again.
What? I don't get it.
It's disgusting. Please stop.
Don't you really live with your boyfriend?
I live alone.
Why don't you try a more serious makeover?
My neighbor makes a false accusation that I make strange noises in the middle of the night.
I'm also sleeping late at night.
What do you like Grameen?
Oh, yeah.
This one.
My mom bought it for me when I was a kid.
Don't tell me your name.
Don't tell me.
Cute.
Don't worry about your sweet mama.
Okay, okay.
Hana's a grown woman now.
Yeah.
Ah...
Hmm?
It's none of your business.
I know what you mean.
What's with this guy?
Shut up! Shut up!
You don't know what's going on!
I don't feel well, so I'm done for today.
Okay, flapjacks.
Ah...
Ready for a snack.
Ready to eat snack.
Ready to eat snack
Thank you for watching today.
See you in the next video.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching.
Shutter sound
Oops.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoa. Whoa.
ohohohohohoh...
est
voodoo
I'm so sorry.
You noticed.
You've been asleep long enough.
You don't need to be awake right now.
You're afraid of getting hurt
You're always taking advantage of people.
You're so fragile
You're pathetic.
Stop it. Stop it.
You're weak.
I'm not weak.
I'm weak.I'm weak.
I'm not weak!
Thank you for watching.
Let's get out of here.